A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2000:016: Grants and General Files, 1968-1998; 8; 42.05 Cubic Feet 32 standard record storage boxes.
  - Markle Foundation - Monroe Price - Book on International Broadcasting, 1992-1997 (Box 174, Folder 12-13)
  - Markle Foundation - Making of the President '96 (J95325), 1995-1997 (Box 175, Folder 1-4)
  - Markle Foundation - Communications Policy Essays (D95322), 1995-1998 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Markle Foundation - Sesame Street Archive (D95320, D95209), 1995-1998; Digital media. (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Markle Foundation - Making of the President (D95319), 1995 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Markle Foundation - Connors - Online Marketing Study (D95208), 1994-1995 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Markle Foundation - Reinventing America (REUS) (J95110), 1994-1997 (Box 175, Folder 9-14)
  - Markle Foundation - Online Interactive Game (D95105), 1994-1995 (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Markle Foundation - Schwartz - Online Computer Network (D95103), 1994 (Box 175, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - Public Affairs Programming - American Political Channel (G95004), 1994-1996 (Box 176, Folder 1-4)
  - Markle Foundation - Harvard Meeting on Media and the '96 Election (D94328), 1994-1995 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Markle Foundation - Communications Technology Study (G94329), 1994-1996 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Markle Foundation - Media and Politics - Democracy in America (D94327), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Markle Foundation - SimHealth (D94322), 1994 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Markle Foundation - Online Interactive Programming (G94225) - Crossover, 1994-1995 (Box 176, Folder 9-10)
  - Markle Foundation - Election '96 - Sales and Marketing Plan (J94223, J94224), 1994-1995 (Box 176, Folder 11-12)
  - Markle Foundation - Political Campaign Communication Reform (G93228, D94213), 1993-1994 (Box 176, Folder 13-15)
  - Markle Foundation - Election Project (J94223), 1994-1995 (Box 176, Folder 16-17)
  - Markle Foundation - Public Agenda Foundation - Electronic Town Meeting (J93334), 1993-1994 (Box 182, Folder 3-4)
  - Markle Foundation - Telecommunications Policy Studies (G93336), 1993-1996 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Markle Foundation - Election '96 - SimHealth (J941110, J93224), 1993-1996; Digital media (Box 182, Folder 6-8)
  - Markle Foundation - Election '96 - SimHealth - Maxis - Thinking Tools, 1994-1995; Digital media (Box 182, Folder 9-10)
  - Markle Foundation - SimHealth - Maxis - Development and Distribution, 1993-1998; Digital media (Box 182, Folder 11-14)
  - Markle Foundation - SimHealth - Marketing and Promotion, 1993-1995 (Box 183, Folder 1-5)
  - Markle Foundation - SimHealth - Maxis - Checks and Backup, 1993-1994 (Box 183, Folder 6-8)
  - Markle Foundation - Majic Bus CD (D93329), 1993 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Markle Foundation - Public Broadcasting and Political Programming - Weinberg (D93322), 1993 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Markle Foundation - Public Interest, Cable TV - Brown - Documentary Channel (D93220), 1993 (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Markle Foundation - Homet - Campaign Communications Reform (D93107, D93219, D93103), 1992-1995 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Permutter, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1-2)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - PBS Initiative (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - PBS Initiative - Fundraising Activities and Outreach, 1990-1991 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Publicity, 1990-1992 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - PBS Initiative - PBS-CPB Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323), 1990-1993 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Permutter - The PBS Election Project (3 vol.), 1991 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Follow-Up, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - National Citizen's Committee, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Promotion, Public Relations (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Henry Geller's Opinions re: PBS, Equal Opportunity, 1989-1991 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Post-PBS Activities, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - MIT Meeting, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 14)
  - 2017:FA785:011 - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - MIT Meeting - Audio Tapes, 1991 July 10; Audio. (Box 2017:FA785:011)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Original Backgrounder and TVC Prospectus, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 15)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Advisory Board, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 16)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Louis Harris Correspondence, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 17)
  - Markle Foundation - The Voters Channel (G90323) - Proposals Referred to Permutter, 1990-1991 (Box 189, Folder 18)
  - Markle Foundation - Multimedia Lab - Apple Computer (Box 189, Folder 19)
  - 2017:FA785:012 - Markle Foundation - Multimedia Lab - Apple Computer - Promos 1988-1990, Audio and VHS (Box 2017:FA785:012)
  - University of Massachusetts (G95218) - Children's Television Viewing Survey, 1995-1998 (Box 177, Folder 1-2)
  - University of Massachusetts and University of Kansas (G93225, G93226), 1993-1996 (Box 177, Folder 3-6)
  - Microelectronics and Computer Technology Corp. (MCC) (J93227, J9332), 1993-1994 (Box 177, Folder 7-8)
  - Multimedia Corporation (G90105), 1989-1996 (Box 177, Folder 9-15)
  - Multimedia Corporation (G93108, G93109), 1992-1995 (Box 178, Folder 1-3)
  - Multimedia Corporation (G90105), 1989-1997 (Box 178, Folder 4-8)
  - Multimedia Corporation (G90105) - Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 178, Folder 9-12)
  - Multimedia Corporation (G90105) - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 179, Folder 1-4)
  - Multimedia Corporation, 1994-1997 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG), 1992-1998 (Box 183, Folder 13-14)
  - New York University (NYU) (D93331), 1993-1994 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1995-1998 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern University - High Fever (G96334), 1996-1999 (Box 184, Folder 3-4)
  - National Video Resources, Inc., 1996 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - NeoStar, 1995 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - University of New Mexico, 1995-1996 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - The New School for Social Research, 1977-1992 (Box 188, Folder 4-5)
  - The City of New York - General, 1991-1992 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - New York City Partnership, 1989-1991 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - New York Law School, 1974-1992 (Box 188, Folder 8-9)
  - New York Community Trust, 1990-1993 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - New York Medical College, 1995 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - The New York Observer, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - The New York Media Association, 1996 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - New York Public Library, 1990-1994 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG), 1987-1994 (Box 188, Folder 15-21)
  - New York State Telephone Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 188, Folder 22)
  - New York Times, 1974-1993 (Box 188, Folder 23-24)
  - The New York Times Company Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 25)
  - New York University (NYU), 1976-1995 (Box 188, Folder 26-29)
  - Pensioners - Griffin, Mae, 1983-1999 (Box 179, Folder 6-7)
    Restricted - Personnel material
  - Pensioners (Box 179, Folder 8-10)
  - University of Pennsylvania (G92338), 1992-1997 (Box 179, Folder 11-12)
  - 2017:FA785:009 - University of Pennsylvania (G92338) - Annenberg School of Communications - News Coverage of Political Ads: Helping the Electorate Make Sense of Political Advertisements, VHS (Box 2017:FA785:009)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G97333), 1997-1998 (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G98108), 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G95328), 1995-1996 (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G95102), 1994-1995 (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G94104), 1993-1994 (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G93105), 1992-1993 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G93110), 1992-1994 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - The Public Agenda Foundation (G93116), 1992-1993 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Public Broadcasting Feasibility Study (J96004) - Grossman, 1995-1996 (Box 219, Folder 1-3)
  - Radio for Youth Foundation (D92332), 1992-1997 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - RAND Corporation - Secure Communications Workshop (G97335), 1997-1998 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - RAND Corporation (G93333), 1993-1996 (Box 180, Folder 6-8)
  - Rutgers University (G96332) (Box 180, Folder 9-10)
  - Rutgers University (G98329), 1998-1999 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Rutgers University (G98217), 1997-1998 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Rutgers University (D93332), 1993-1998 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Rutgers University (D93217), 1992-1994 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - SeniorNet (G94331), 1994-1998 (Box 180, Folder 15-19)
  - SeniorNet (G94102), 1993-1994 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Research Council (G92342), 1992-1996 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University - Center for Economic Policy Research (G94336), 1994-1997 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Policy Research Conference (TPRC) (G95330), 1995-1998 (Box 181, Folder 4-5)
  - Telecommunications Policy Research Conference (TPRC) (G95330) - Conference Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 181, Folder 6-9)
  - The Trans-Atlantic Broadcasting Foundation (D92106), 1991-1992 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - The Voyager Company (G91331), 1991-1997 (Box 181, Folder 11-12)
  - The Voyager Company (G89324), 1981; 1989-1997 (Box 181, Folder 13-15)
  - Yeshiva University - Cardoza School of Law - Monroe Price - Center for Media, Law and Policy, 1995-1997 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - York University - Glendon College (PRI), 1992 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous - Children's Television Workshop - Proposals and Reports, 1968-1970; 1996 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous - All Media Dramatic Workshop (G78102) - Final Report, 1979 (Box 184, Folder 6-7)
  - Miscellaneous - CNN - Democracy in America (G92005) - Report and Clippings, 1992 (Box 184, Folder 8-11)
  - Miscellaneous - Markle Foundation - Classification of Grants and Index, 1969-1983 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous - Markle Foundation - Market Study, SeniorNet - Final Report, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous - Statistical Report Leading Up to Aging in America (G87104), 1987 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous - The Markle Foundation - Political Advertising Study, Wave I, II, III, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous - Alice Allen Project - Computer Discs, Lloyd Morrisset essays, Board Dinner, April 30, 1997 Speech, Digital media. (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous - Publications and Reports, 1978-1998 (Box 187)
- Accession 2008:073, 1989-2006; 9; 38.11 Cubic Feet 28 standard record storage boxes, boxes 190-217.
  Arranged in 14 subseries by program area/subject.
  - Policy for a Networked Society, 1
    - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences (CASS) - Prof. Xia Yong (993034BP), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 1-5)
    - Oxford University - Monroe Price (993041BG), 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (001001DG), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Technology Alliance of Washington - Edward Fritzky (001004DG), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Markle Foundation-Program Exploration - Andrew Blau (001005DE), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - ICANN - Zoe Baird (001010BP), 1999; Includes digital media. (Box 190, Folder 10-11)
    - Markle Foundation-Internet Governance Project - Center for Democracy and Technology-Common Cause - Jerry Berman (001010BP-C and C2), 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 12-13)
    - The Berkman Center for Internet and Society - Eric Saltzman (001010BP-D), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - American Library Association - Nancy Kranich (001010BP-E), 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Common Cause - Meredith McGehee (001010BP-F), 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Common Cause Education Fund-CDT - Scott Harshbarger (001010BP-F2), 2000 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Carter Center - Charles Costello (001010BP-G), 1999 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Carter Center - Charles Costello (001010BP-G2), 2000 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, Inc. - Amy Hastings (001010BP-H), 1999; Includes digital media. (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - The Berkman Center for Internet and Society - Eric Saltzman (001010BP-I), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - ACLU Foundation - Barry Steinhardt (001010BP-J), 2000-2001 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - The Center for Democracy and Technology - Berman and Dempsey (001022DG), 1999 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Rock the Vote - Mario Velasquez (001026DG), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - American Public and the Internet - Zoe Baird (002028BP), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkely School of Law - Herma Hill Kay (002029BP-B), 2000-2003 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University - Lawrence Lessig (002029BP-C), 2001-2003 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - American University - Peter Jaszi (002029BP-D), 2000-2003; Includes digital media. (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - World Resource Institute - Allen Hammond (002036DG), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Oxford University - Stefaan Verhulst (003042BG), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Internet Governance Project - Internet Policy Institute - Andrew Shapiro (011010BP), 1999-2000 (Box 191, Folder 11-16)
    - National Consumer Law Center - Willard Ogburn (011010DG), 2000-2001 (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - The Berkman Center for Internet and Society - Eric Saltzman (001011DG), 2000-2001 (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Law School - Larry Lessig (001013DG), 2000 (Box 191, Folder 19)
    - Markle Foundation-Internet Governance Project II - Zoe Baird (012042BP), 2002-2003 (Box 191, Folder 20)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Jerry Berman (012042BP-A1), 2000-2001 (Box 191, Folder 21)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Jerry Berman (012042BP-A1), 2000-2001 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Common Cause Education Fund - Scott Harshbarger (012042BP-A2), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Oxford University - Monroe Price (012042BP-A3), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Jerry Berman (012042BP-A4), 2002-2003 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Salzburg Seminar - Olin Robinson (012042BP-C), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - University of Massachusetts - Ethan Katsh (012042BP-D1), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Syracuse University - Milton Mueller (012042BP-D2), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - New America Foundation - Ted Halstead (012042BP-F), 2001-2003 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Jerry Berman (012042BP-H), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Oxford University - Monroe Price (012042BP-I1), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - National Consumer Law Center - Margot Saunders (012042BP-J1), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Oquirrh Institute - Mike Leavitt (012042BP-K1), 2001-2003 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Oquirrh Institute - Mike Leavitt (012042BP-K1), 2001-2003; Includes digital media. (Box 192, Folder 13-14)
    - Oxford University - Price Monroe (012042BP-K2), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Mary Rundle - Mary Rundle (012042BP-K3), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Center for Democracy and Technology - Jim Dempsey (012042BP-K4), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Common Cause Education - Scott Harshburger (012042BP-K5), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Oxford University - Monroe Price - Verhulst (012042BP-L1), 2001 (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Carter Center - Charles Costello (012042BP-L2), 2001-2002 (Box 192, Folder 20)
    - Salzburg Seminar - Kevin Hurley (012042BP-M1), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 21)
    - Mindbeam - Kristin Van Hook (012042BP-N), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 22)
    - ICANN - Tamar Frankel (012042BP-O), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 23)
    - Autonomedia - James Fleming (012042BP-P), 2002 (Box 192, Folder 24)
    - Yeshiva University - Monroe Price (012042BP-Q), 2002-2003 (Box 192, Folder 25)
    - Consultant for ICANN - Akash Kapur (012042BP-R), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Center for Global Studies - Barry Carin (012042BP-S), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Salzburg Seminar - ICANN Travel - Kevin Hurley (012042BP-T), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - AKK Associates LLC - Akash Kapur (012042BP-U), 2003 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Legal Aid for Washington (Law) Fund - Rebecca Modini (013047DG), 2001 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (013049DG), 2001 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Internet Society - Martin Kupres (013062BPC-L), 2002; Includes digital media. (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Leslie Gelb (013062BPC-M), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Council on Foreign Relations: Terrorism Website - Leslie Gelb (013062BP-P), 2001-2002 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Consultant: Andrew Shapiro - Andrew Shapiro (020302DE), 2001 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Rock the Vote Foundation Fund - Mario Velasquez (022015DG), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Council on Competitiveness-Forum on Technology and Innovation - Senator Jay Rockefeller (022019DG), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (023025DG), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Internoded - Tara Sonenshine (023027BP-D), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Edelman Public Relations - Daniel Edelman (023027BP-E), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - SwanDiveDigital - Brian Reisinger (023027BP-L), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - SwanDiveDigital - Brian Reisinger (023027BP-M), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - Washington State Bar Association - Joan Fairbanks (023030DG), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 18)
    - Clay Shirky - Program Exploration II (030218DE), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 19)
    - Program Exploration III - Joanna McIntosh (030305DE), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Law School - Larry Lessig (030306DE), 2003 (Box 193, Folder 21)
    - Markle Lectures - Steven Clift (031004DP), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 22)
    - Stanford University - Open Spectrum Project - Lawrence Lessig (031006DP), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 23)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (031007DP), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 24)
    - Internet Education Foundation - Jerry Berman (031011BP-B), 2002 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - ACLU Foundation - Berry Steinhardt (031011BP-C), 2003 (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (032018DG), 2003 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Vital Voices - Elizabeth O'Connell (033022DG), 2003 (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Mindshare - Dan Solomon (033023DP), 2003-2004 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - The Aspen Institute - Charles Firestone (033024DG), 2003-2004 (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - The Aspen Institute - Walter Isaacson (041001DG), 2003 (Box 209, Folder 19)
  - Communications and Political Participation, 2
    - Golden Jubilee Commission on Telecommunications - Max D. Paglin (D93323), 1993 (Box 193, Folder 25)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Shanto Iyengar (D97213), 1996-1997 (Box 193, Folder 26)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Shanto Iyengar (D97330), 1997-1998 (Box 193, Folder 27)
    - North Carolina State University-Entman, Robert - Robert Entman (G95106), 1995-1998 (Box 193, Folder 28)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Shanto Iyengar (G96333), 1996-1998 (Box 193, Folder 29)
    - The Public Agenda Foundation - Deborah Wadsworth (G96336), 1996-1999 (Box 193, Folder 30-31)
    - Center for Media and Public Affairs - Bob Lichter (G97110), 1996-1998 (Box 193, Folder 32-33)
  - Public Affairs, 3
    - Vinca LaFleur (013062BPC-F), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 34)
    - Chermayeff and Geismar Inc - Ivan Chermayeff (013062BPC-H), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 35)
    - Public Affairs Consultant - John Glassie (023027BP-B), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 36)
    - Consulting Contract to Public Affairs - Tara Sonenshine (023027BP-G), 2003 (Box 193, Folder 37)
    - Burness Communications - Andy Burness (023027BP-H), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 38)
    - J. Walter Thompson - Sheri Mason (023027BP-I), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 39)
    - President's Letter - Lani Kennedy (023027BP-J), 2002 (Box 193, Folder 40)
    - Airfoil Public Relations - Jeanne-Marie Baron (023027BP-K), 2002-2003 (Box 193, Folder 41)
    - SwanDiveDigital - Brian Reisinger (023027BP-N), 2003 (Box 193, Folder 42)
    - Airfoil Public Relations - Jeanne-Marie Baron (023027BP-O), 2003 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - SwanDiveDigital - Brian Reisinger (023027BP-Q), 2003-2004 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - 375 Events, LLC - John Battelle (031011BP-A - 023027BP-A), 2002 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Public Engagement, 4
    - The Children's Partnership- Tides Center - Laurie Lipper (011004DG), 2000 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Bobbie Greene (012033DG), 2000-2001; Includes digital media. (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Twentieth Century Fund Foundation - Mort Halperin (D98107), 1997-1998 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Markle Foundation - Interactive Educational Products - Siegel and Gale - Lloyd Morrisett (J98110), 1997-1998 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Sesame Workshop - Morrisett (G98115), 1997-2002 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - California Institute of Tech. - Bruce Murray (BJ98332), 1998 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Thirteen-WNET - Barbara O'Keefe (BJ99109), 1998 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - MOUSE - Andrew Rasiej (DG993033), 1999 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Internews - David Hoffman (993042BG), 1999 (Box 194, Folder 12-13)
    - Link Media - David Hoffman (BG99342), 1999 (Box 194, Folder 14-15)
    - Markle Foundation-Internews - Zoe Baird (993047BP), 1999 (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Educational Netcasting Foundation -Harvard University - Henry Louis Gates, Jr. (002031BP-C), 2000 (Box 194, Folder 17-18)
    - Markle Foundation - Active Lab Initiative (001015BP), 1989 (Box 194, Folder 19)
  - Program Exploration, 5
    - Markle Program Exploration - Barbara O'Keefe (PEJ0101), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
    - Markle Foundation Program Exploration - Atul Gawande (PEJ0102), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Markle Foundation Program Exploration: Health Data - Andrew Blau (PEJ0103), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Markle Foundation Program Exploration: Internet Economy - Andrew Blau (PEJ0104), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Markle Foundation Program Exploration: Communications Plan - John Glassie (PEJ0105), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Markle Foundation- Interact, Democracy, Civil Society- Weisberg - Julia Moffett (PEJ0202-99020), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Committee to Project Journalism - Lucy Meyer Harrop (PEJ0203), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation- Journalism and Implications of Convergence - Julia Moffett (PEJ0204), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation- Citizens in the Inforamtion Age - Andrew Shapiro (PEJ0205), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundatation- Expanding Global Citizens - Julia Moffett (PEJ0206), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation- Culture and Leadership - Julia Moffett (PEJ0207), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation- Citizens in the Inforamtion Age - Andrew Blau (PEJ0208), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Markle Foundation- Communication Environment- John Carey - John Carey (PEJ0210), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Markle Foundation- Y2K - Julia Moffett (PEJ0211), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Markle Foundation- Andrew Shapiro - Andrew Shapiro (PEJ0212-99021), 1999 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Markle Foundation - Program Exploration - Children's Research Fund (PEJ0213) (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Program Planning - Zoe Baird (BJ98114), 1998-1999 (Box 195, Folder 5)